Finding Aid for the John Phillip Hyatt Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Subject Files
  - Publishing Activities
    - Journals--Religion in Life--Agendas and Reports (Box 13, File 17-18)
    - Journals--Religion in Life--Meeting Minutes (Box 13, File 19)
    - Journals--Religion in Life--Miscellaneous (Box 13, File 20)
    - Journals--Theological Education in America (Box 13, File 21)
    - Sunday School Materials (Box 13, File 22)
    - Miscellaneous Contracts (Box 13, File 23)
    - Miscellaneous Reading Reports (Box 13, File 24)
  - Bible Translation Activities
    - History of English Bible (Box 14, File 1-2)
    - Method and Issues (Box 14, File 3)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Book of Job (Box 14, File 4-7)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Book of Psalms (you/your problem) (Box 14, File 8)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1959)—Agendas (Box 14, File 9-11)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1959)—Changes (Box 14, File 12)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1959)--Suggestions (Box 14, File 13)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1965)—Agenda (Box 14, File 14)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1965)--Suggestions (Box 14, File 15)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1968) (Box 14, File 16)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1970)—Agenda (Box 14, File 17)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1970)—Suggested Changes (Box 14, File 18-19)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1972)—Agendas (Old Testament) (Box 14, File 20)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1972)—Agendas (New Testament) (Box 14, File 21)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1972)—Changes N Approved (Box 14, File 22-23)
  - Bible Translation Activities
    - Standard Bible Committee—Meetings (1972)—Suggested Changes (Box 15, File 1)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Membership, etc. (Box 15, File 2)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Memoranda (Box 15, File 3)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Minutes (Box 15, File 4)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Notes (Box 15, File 5)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Reports (Box 15, File 6)
    - Standard Bible Committee—2nd Edition (1972) (Box 15, File 7)
    - Standard Bible Committee—Miscellaneous (Box 15, File 8)
    - Versions—Berkeley (Box 15, File 9)
    - Versions—Confraternity Edition (Box 15, File 10)
    - Versions—Dartmouth Bible (Box 15, File 11)
    - Versions—Jerusalem Bible (Box 15, File 12)
    - Versions—Jewish (Box 15, File 13)
    - Versions—King James (Box 15, File 14)
    - Versions—King James II (Box 15, File 15)
    - Versions—New English Bible (Box 15, File 16)
    - Versions—New International Version (Box 15, File 17)
    - Versions—New Schofield (Box 15, File 18)
    - Versions—RSV—Catholic Edition—Miscellaneous (Box 15, File 19)
    - Versions—RSV—Catholic Edition—Clippings (Box 15, File 20)
    - Versions—RSV—Celebration Services (Box 15, File 21)
    - Versions—RSV—Liturgical and Educational Use (Box 15, File 22)
    - Versions—RSV—Magazine Articles (Box 15, File 23)
    - Versions--RSV--Newspaper Clippings (Box 15, File 24-25)
    - Versions--RSV--Pamphlets--Con (Box 15, File 26-27)
    - Versions—RSV—Pamphlets—Pro (Box 15, File 28)
    - Versions—RSV—Press Releases (Box 15, File 29)
    - Versions—Today's English Version (Box 15, File 30)
    - Versions—Miscellaneous (Box 15, File 31)
- Academic Career
  - Teaching Responsibilities—Class Materials
    - Ancient Near Eastern Texts (Rel. 390a) (Box 16, File 1-3)
    - Aramaic (Div. 322) (Box 16, File 4)
    - Archaeology of the Old Testament (Box 16, File 5-7)
    - Biblical Archaeology (Rel. 308) (Box 16, File 8)
    - Communism Seminar (Box 16, File 9)
    - Egyptology (Box 16, File 10)
    - Exodus (Rel. 390a) (Box 16, File 11-12)
    - Gospels (Box 16, File 13-14)
    - Hebrew Prophets (Rel. 501) (Box 16, File 15)
    - Hebrew Prophets—Jeremiah (Rel. 301) (Box 16, File 16)
    - Hosea (Box 16, File 17)
    - introduction to the Old Testament (Rel. 251b) (Box 16, File 18)
    - Jeremiah (Rel. 390a) (Box 16, File 19)
    - Judaism in New Testament Times (Box 16, File 20)
    - Messianism (Rel. 384) (Box 16, File 21)
    - Methods of Biblical Criticism (Rel. 500) (Box 16, File 22)
    - Methods of Biblical Criticism (Rel. 300) (Box 16, File 23-26)
  - Teaching Responsibilities—Class Materials
    - Methods of Old Testament Criticism (Rel. 300) (Box 17, File 1-3)
    - New Testament History and Literature (Lee Keck) (Box 17, File 4-6)
    - Old Testament (Rel. 451) (Box 17, File 7)
    - Old Testament Exegesis (Box 17, File 8)
    - Old Testament History and Literature (Rel. 251) (Box 17, File 9-16)
    - Old Testament Theology (Box 17, File 17)
    - Religion of the Old Testament (Box 17, File 18)
    - Senior Seminar (Box 17, File 19)
    - Wisdom Literature (Div. 303) (Box 17, File 20)
    - Class Lists (Box 17, File 21)
  - Teaching Responsibilities—Class Materials
    - Grade Sheets (Box 18, File 1-3)
    - Miscellaneous Examinations (Box 18, File 4)
    - Miscellaneous Reserve Book Lists (Box 18, File 5)
    - Student Dissertations (Box 18, File 6-7)
    - Student Papers (Butler - Darnell) (Box 18, File 8)
    - Student Papers (Fowler - Neil) (Box 18, File 8)
    - Student Papers (Oliver) (Box 18, File 9)
    - Student Papers (Osterfield - Owen) (Box 18, File 10)
    - Student Papers (Perdue - Wright) (Box 18, File 11)
    - Southern Methodist University (Box 18, File 12)
    - University of Chicago (Box 18, File 13)
    - Wellesley College (Box 18, File 14)
    - Qualifying Exams (Box 18, File 15-18)
    - Reading Lists (Box 18, File 19)
  - Administrative Responsibilities
    - Books--Advertisements (Box 19, File 1)
    - Books--Orders (Box 19, File 2)
    - Divinity School--Accreditation (Box 19, File 3)
    - Divinity School--Administrative Committee (Box 19, File 4)
    - Divinity School--Admissions Committee (Box 19, File 5)
    - Divinity School--John Keith Benton (Box 19, File 6)
    - Divinity School--Black Studies Committee (Box 19, File 7)
    - Divinity School--Chapel Committee (Box 19, File 8)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Course Listings (Box 19, File 9)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Course Offerings (Box 19, File 10)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Memoranda (Box 19, File 11)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Minutes (Box 19, File 12)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Papers (Box 19, File 13)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Proposals (Box 19, File 14)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Reports (Box 19, File 15)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Requests and Responses (Box 19, File 16)
    - Divinity School--Curriculum Committee--Miscellaneous (Box 19, File 17)
    - Divinity School--Dean Search Committee (1956) (Box 19, File 18)
    - Divinity School--Dean Search Committee (1964-65)--Vitae (Box 19, File 19)
    - Divinity School--Dean Search Committee (1964-65)--Memoranda, Notes, etc. (Box 19, File 20)
    - Divinity School--Faculty Appointments--Memoranda and Miscellaneous (Box 19, File 21)
    - Divinity School--Faculty Appointments--Vitae (Box 19, File 22-23)
    - Divinity School--Faculty Biography Forms (Box 19, File 24)
    - Divinity School--Faculty Meetings--Agendas (Box 19, File 25)
    - Divinity School--Faculty Meetings--Minutes (Box 19, File 26-27)
  - Administrative Responsibilities
    - Divinity School--Faculty Meetings--Minutes (Box 20, File 1-7)
    - Divinity School--Faculty Newsletter (Box 20, File 8)
    - Divinity School--Finance Committee (Box 20, File 9)
    - Divinity School--Grading Policy (Box 20, File 10)
    - Divinity School--Hawkins Testimonial Dinner (Box 20, File 11)
    - Divinity School--Lawson Case--Press Releases, Memoranda, etc. (Box 20, File 12)
    - Divinity School--Lawson Case--Newspaper Clippings (Box 20, File 13)
    - Divinity School--Lawson Case--Publications (Box 20, File 14)
    - Divinity School--Lay Theological Education (Box 20, File 15)
    - Divinity School--Library (Box 20, File 16)
    - Divinity School--Library Committee (Box 20, File 17)
    - Divinity School--Oberlin Merger (Box 20, File 18)
    - Divinity School--Orientation (Box 20, File 19)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Committee Assignments (Box 20, File 20)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Course Evaluations (Box 20, File 21)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee-- Course Loads and Offerings (Box 20, File 22)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Faculty Appointments--Black Studies (Box 20, File 23)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Faculty Appointments--Sallie TeSelle (Box 20, File 24)
  - Administrative Responsibilities
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee-- Faculty Appointments--Memoranda (Box 21, File 1)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee-- Faculty Evaluations (Box 21, File 2-3)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee-- Meeting Agendas (Box 21, File 4)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee-- Minutes (Box 21, File 5-7)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Memoranda (Box 21, File 8)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Sewanee (Box 21, File 9)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Leave Requests (Box 21, File 10)
    - Divinity School--Personnel and Policy Committee--Miscellaneous (Box 21, File 11)
    - Divinity School--Planning Committee (Box 21, File 12)
    - Divinity School--Professional Studies Committee (Box 21, File 13)
    - Divinity School--Psychological Testing (Box 21, File 14)
    - Divinity School--Publications--Prospectus (Box 21, File 15-16)
    - Divinity School--Publications--Miscellaneous (Box 21, File 17-18)
    - Divinity School--Quadrangle Dedication (Box 21, File 19)
    - Divinity School--Racial Segregation (Box 21, File 20)
    - Divinity School--Sealantic Grant (Box 21, File 21)
  - Administrative Responsibilities
    - Divinity School--Student Life and Activities Committee (Box 22, File 1)
    - Divinity School--Student Lists (Box 22, File 2)
    - Divinity School--Worship Services (Box 22, File 3)
    - Divinity School--Miscellaneous Memoranda (Box 22, File 4)
    - Divinity School--Miscellaneous Proposals, Reports, etc. (Box 22, File 5)
    - Divinity School--Miscellaneous (Box 22, File 6)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Admissions Applications (Box 22, File 7)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Alumni/ae (Box 22, File 8)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Richard Batey (Box 22, File 9)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Graduate Record Exams (Box 22, File 10)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Hillel Professor (Box 22, File 11)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Ho Angelos (Box 22, File 12)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Language Exams (Box 22, File 13)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Faculty Meeting Minutes (Box 22, File 14-17)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Memoranda (Box 22, File 18)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Qualifying Exams (Box 22, File 19)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Scholarships (Box 22, File 20)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Sealantic Fellowships (Box 22, File 21)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Student Lists (Box 22, File 22)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Teaching Assistants (Box 22, File 23)
    - Graduate Department of Religion-- Teaching Vacancy Lists (Box 22, File 24)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Theses in Progress (Box 22, File 25)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Transfer Credit (Box 22, File 26)
    - Graduate Department of Religion--Miscellaneous (Box 22, File 27)
    - Grants--Announcements, etc. (Box 22, File 28)
    - Grants--Hyatt Reports and Applications, etc. (Box 22, File 29)
    - Grants--Other Faculty Members (Box 22, File 30)
    - Grants--Recommendations (Box 22, File 31)
    - Sabbatical (1967-68) (Box 22, File 32)
    - University--Athletic Committee--Minutes, Memoranda (Box 22, File 33)
  - Administrative Responsibilities
    - University--Athletic Committee--Reports (Box 23, File 1)
    - University--Harvie Branscomb (Box 23, File 2)
    - University--Branscomb Award (Box 23, File 3)
    - University--Chancellor Committee--Conversation Reports (Box 23, File 4)
    - University--Chancellor Committee--Vitae (Box 23, File 5-6)
    - University--Chancellor Committee--Miscellaneous (Box 23, File 7)
    - University--Ford Ph.D. Program (Box 23, File 8)
    - University--Graduate Faculty Council--Memoranda, Minutes (Box 23, File 9)
    - University--Graduate Faculty Council--Reports, etc. (Box 23, File 10)
    - University--Humanities Area Committee (Box 23, File 11)
    - University--Medical School (Box 23, File 12)
    - University--School of Nursing (Box 23, File 13)
    - University--Organization and Rules (Box 23, File 14)
    - University--Peabody College (Box 23, File 15)
    - University--Publications--Calendar (Box 23, File 16)
    - University--Publications--Vanderbilt Gazette (Box 23, File 17-21)
    - University--Research Council--Carnegie Foundation-Application Lists, etc. (Box 23, File 22)
    - University--Research Council--Carnegie Foundation-Memoranda (Box 23, File 23)
    - University--Research Council--Carnegie Foundation-Reports (Box 23, File 24)
    - University--Research Council--Carnegie Foundation-Rules (Box 23, File 25)
    - University--Research Counci1--Memoranda, Miscellaneous (Box 23, File 26)
    - University--Research Council--Reports (Box 23, File 27)
  - Administrative Responsibilities
    - University--Research Council--Rules (Box 24, File 1)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Appointments and Promotions--Drafts (Box 24, File 2)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Appointments and Promotions--Memoranda and Miscellaneous (Box 24, File 3)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Calendar Changes (Box 24, File 4)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Education Program (Box 24, File 5)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Fixed Term Administrative Appointments--Faculty Responses (Box 24, File 6-7)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Fixed Term Administrative Appointments--Reports and Miscellaneous (Box 24, File 8)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Graduate School of Management (Box 24, File 9)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Linguistics Program (Box 24, File 10)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Master of Teaching in Engineering Program (MET) (Box 24, File 11)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Master of Management Program (Box 24, File 12)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Medical School (Box 24, File 13)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Minutes (Box 24, File 14)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Non-Thesis Masters Degree (Box 24, File 15)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Planning Study (Box 24, File 16)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--ROTC Report (Box 24, File 17)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--University Professorship (Box 24, File 18)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Notes (Box 24, File 19)
    - University--Senate--Academic Policy Committee--Miscellaneous Memoranda, Reports, etc. (Box 24, File 20)
    - University--Senate--Constitution and Organization (Box 24, File 21)
    - University--Senate--Executive Committee (Box 24, File 22)
    - University--Senate--Meeting Minutes (Box 24, File 23)
    - University--Senate--Miscellaneous Reports, Memoranda, etc. (Box 24, File 24)
    - University--Travel Expenses (Box 24, File 25)
    - University--Veterans Council--Memoranda (Box 24, File 26)
    - University--Veterans Council--Reports (Box 24, File 27)
    - University--Miscellaneous Reports, Proposals, etc. (Box 24, File 28)
    - University of Chicago--Department of Oriental Languages (Box 24, File 29)
    - University of Chicago--Divinity School (Box 24, File 30)
  - Organizations
    - American Association of Theological Schools-- Bulletins and Reports (Box 25, File 1)
    - AATS--Committee on Advanced Theological Study--Christian Education/Pastoral Ministry (Box 25, File 2)
    - AATS--Committee on Advanced Theological Study--Doctoral Degree (Box 25, File 3)
    - AATS--Committee on Advanced Theological Study--Enrollment (Box 25, File 4)
    - AATS--Committee on Advanced Theological Study--Masters Degree (Box 25, File 5)
    - AATS--Committee on Advanced Theological Study-- Meeting Minutes (Box 25, File 6-7)
    - AATS--Committee on Advanced Theological Study--Miscellaneous (Box 25, File 8)
    - AATS--Miscellaneous (Box 25, File 9)
    - American Bible Society (Box 25, File 10)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 25, File 11)
    - American Oriental Society--Annual Meetings (Box 25, File 12)
    - American Oriental Society--Paper Abstracts (Box 25, File 13)
    - American Oriental Society--Miscellaneous (Box 25, File 14)
    - American School of Oriental Research (ASOR)--Annual Reports and Budgets (Box 25, File 15)
    - ASOR--Memoranda (Box 25, File 16)
    - ASOR--Meeting Minutes (Box 25, File 17-19)
    - ASOR--Newsletters (Box 25, File 20-24)
  - Organizations
    - ASOR--Newsletters (Box 26, File 1-7)
    - ASOR--Reports (Box 26, File 8-9)
    - ASOR--Miscellaneous (Box 26, File 10)
    - Baylor University--Graduate Programs (Box 26, File 11-14)
    - Baylor University--Miscellaneous (Box 26, File 15)
    - Christian Faith and Life Community (Box 26, File 16)
    - Civitan Club (Box 26, File 17)
    - Committee on Graduate Studies in Religion (CGSR)--Meeting Minutes (Box 26, File 18-21)
    - Committee on Graduate Studies in Religion--Miscellaneous (Box 26, File 22)
    - Delta Ministry (Box 26, File 23)
    - Fellowship of Southern Churchmen (Box 26, File 24)
  - Organizations
    - Hebrew Union College--Jerusalem--Newsletter (Box 27, File 1-3)
    - Hebrew Union College--Jerusalem--Miscellaneous (Box 27, File 4)
    - Institute for Mediterranean Studies (Box 27, File 5)
    - Inter-University Committee on Israel (Box 27, File 6)
    - International Organization for the Study of the Old Testament (Box 27, File 7)
    - Jewish Palestine Exploration Society (Box 27, File 8)
    - Memphis Theological Seminary (Box 27, File 9)
    - National Association of Biblical Instructors (Box 27, File 10)
    - National Association of Professors of Hebrew (Box 27, File 11)
    - National Council on Religion in Higher Education (NCRHE)--Fellows Lists (Box 27, File 12-13)
    - NCRHE--Memoranda (Box 27, File 14)
    - NCRHE--Newsletters (Box 27, File 15-17)
    - NCRHE---Reports (Box 27, File 18)
    - NCRHE--Week of Work (Box 27, File 19-22)
  - Organizations
    - NCRHE--Miscellaneous (Box 28, File 1)
    - Rhodes University (Box 28, File 2)
    - Society of Biblical Literature (SBL) Annual Meetings--Paper Abstracts (Box 28, File 3-7)
    - SBL--Annual Meetings--Papers Presented, Notes, etc. (Box 28, File 8)
    - SBL--Annual Meetings--Proceedings (Box 28, File 9)
    - SBL--Annual Meetings--Programs (Box 28, File 10-11)
    - SBL--Council Meeting Papers (Box 28, File 12-13)
    - SBL--Membership Lists, etc. (Box 28, File 14)
    - SBL--Memoranda, etc. (Box 28, File 15)
    - SBL--Mid-West Section (Box 28, File 16)
    - SBL--Reports (Box 28, File 17)
    - SBL--Southern Section (Box 28, File 18)
    - SBL--Yonan Codex--Legal Papers, Notes (Box 28, File 19)
    - SBL--Yonan Codex--Memoranda (Box 28, File 20)
    - SBL--Yonan--Codex--Newspaper Clippings, Articles (Box 28, File 21)
  - Organizations
    - Society for Old Testament Study--Bulletins (Box 29, File 1)
    - Society for Old Testament Study--Meetings (Box 29, File 2)
    - Society for Old Testament Study--Miscellaneous (Box 29, File 3)
    - Yale Divinity School--Class Bulletins (Box 29, File 4)
    - Yale Divinity School--Class Lists, etc. (Box 29, File 5)
    - Yale Divinity School--Class Questionnaires (Box 29, File 6-8)
    - Yale Divinity School--Miscellaneous (Box 29, File 9-11)
    - Yale University--Newspaper Clippings (Box 29, File 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29, File 13)
  - Events (Box 29)
    - Chicago School Congress (Vanderbilt Divinity School) (Box 29, File 14)
    - Congress of Religious Education in a New Age (Box 29, File 15)
    - Consultation on Hermeneutics--Bibliography (Box 29, File 16)
    - Consultation on Hermeneutics--Notes (Box 29, File 17)
    - Consultation on Hermeneutics--Papers (Box 29, File 18-21)
    - Consultation on the Teaching of the Biblical Languages (Box 29, File 22)
    - Interdenominational Ministries Institute (Box 29, File 23)
    - Seminar on Revelation as History (Box 29, File 24)
  - Church Activities
    - Disciples of Christ--Conventions (Box 30, File 1)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House-- Dean's Reports (Box 30, File 2-5)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House--Financial Reports (1951-66) (Box 30, File 6)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House--Financial Reports (1967-71) (Box 30, File 7)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House--Miscellaneous (Box 30, File 8)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Constitution (Box 30, File 9)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Financial Reports (Box 30, File 10)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--The Harbinger (Box 30, File 11-12)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Memoranda (Box 30, File 13)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Meeting Agendas (Box 30, File 14)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society-- Meeting Minutes (Box 30, File 15-17)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Phillips Memorial (Box 30, File 18-19)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Planning Committee (Box 30, File 20)
  - Church Activities
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Press Releases (Box 31, File 1)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Reports (Box 31, File 2-4)
    - Disciples of Christ -- Historical Society-- Miscellaneous (Box 31, File 5)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Memoranda (Box 31, File 6)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Minutes (Box 31, File 7)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Study Papers (Box 31, File 8-14)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Miscellaneous (Box 31, File 15)
    - Disciples of Christ--Woodmont Christian Church (Box 31, File 16)
    - Disciples of Christ--Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 31, File 17-18)
    - Ecumenical Concerns--Jewish Materials (Box 31, File 19)
    - Ecumenical Concerns--National Council of Churches (Box 31, File 20)
  - Church Activities
    - Ecumenical Concerns--Roman Catholicism (Box 32, File 1)
    - Ecumenical Concerns--World Council of Churches-- Faith and Order Commission (Box 32, File 2-4)
    - Preaching Engagements--Church Bulletins (Box 32, File 5-6)
- Community Activities
  - Community Relations Conference (Box 32, File 7)
  - South Street Center (Box 32, File 8)
  - Miscellaneous Materials on Race Relations (Box 32, File 9)
  - Various Social Issues (Box 32, File 10)
- Subject Files
  - Alcoholism (Box 33, File 1)
  - Ancient Near East--Assyriology (Box 33, File 2)
  - Ancient Near East--Canaanite Religion (Box 33, File 3)
  - Ancient Near East--Egyptology (Box 33, File 4-5)
  - Ancient Near East--Cyrus Gordon (Box 33, File 6)
  - Ancient Near East--Hittites (Box 33, File 7)
  - Ancient Near East--Mesopotamia (Box 33, File 8-10)
  - Ancient Near East--Palestine, Cultural History of (Box 33, File 11-14)
  - Ancient Near East--Ras Shamra (Box 33, File 15-16)
  - Archaeology--Articles (Box 33, File 17-18)
  - Archaeology--Lachish (Box 33, File 19)
  - Archaeology--Masada (Box 33, File 20)
  - Subject Files